>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以我们在胁迫的形式上结束了我们的整个讨论
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So wrapping up our
whole discussion on types in coercion,
我们正在包围这个单位
we're wrapping up this unit.
让我作最后的评论。
Let me make some final observations.
第一，事实是， JavaScript 有一个动态类型的系统，
Number one, it is true, it is a fact that
JavaScript has a dynamic type system,
它是一种类型的系统，它就是动态的。
it is a type system, it just is dynamic.
当人们说 JavaScript 没有类型的时候我真的很刚毛
I've really bristle when people
say JavaScript has no types,
它确实是，它是一种类型的系统，它不是 Java的类型的系统。
it definitely does, it's a type system,
it's just not Java's type system.
它使用各种形式的胁迫
It uses various forms of coercion but
they're for
值类型转换而不是变量输入。
value type conversions
rather than variable typing.
我们也有可以被强迫的平等比较。
And we also have equality
comparisons that can be coerced.
对 JavaScript 类型系统的普遍响应本质上是避免的
The prevailing response to JavaScript's
type system is essentially avoid as
尽可能多的系统使用三重保护自己
much of the system as possible and
only use the triple to protect yourself so
你不用担心他们的事
that you don't have to worry about them.
我已经说过好几次了，我不认为这是一个有效的策略。
As I've said several times now, I don't
think that that is an effective strategy.
避免任何问题的部分问题，特别是整个单元的问题
Part of the problem with avoidance of
anything but especially an entire unit
就像这种语言一般会有系统地使虫子长期存在
of of the language like that, is that it
tends to systematically perpetuate bugs.
也就是说，不会出现一个错误，或者一个错误不会发生，
That is to say it's not that one bug
will happen or one bug won't happen but
这种心态说，我都不需要了解这个
the mindset that says,
I don't even need to understand this whole
语言的一部分使虫子永久化这是一种系统的方法
part of the language, perpetuates bugs,
that's a systematic approach,
我也不会建议有系统地避免任何特殊的事情
and I would never recommend a systematic
avoidance of any particular thing,
那就是避免对它的理解
that is avoidance of
even understanding it.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我只是相信你不能
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What this boils down to
is that I just believe that you can not
写质量 JavaScript 程序而不了解您的类型。
write quality JavaScript programs
without understanding your types.
您可以编写用于转换和运行但不符合该栏的 JavaScript 程序
You can write JavaScript programs that
shift and run but they don't meet that bar
我认为我们应该在品质上努力除非你明白
of what I think we should be striving for
in quality unless you understand those
除非您的代码的阅读器能够理解这些类型。
types and unless the readers of your
code can understand those types.
所以我们得做点什么
So we have to do something.
我们必须改变我们的编码方式
We've got to change the way
we structure our code.
我们要用这些机制来
We've got to use these mechanisms
that are available to us to
开始向那些打字的人发出信号
start signaling those typing things.
当然你可以去
And of course, you could go
使用整个静态系统 ( 如 typescript 或流) 的所有方法。
all the way to using a whole static type
system, like a typescript or a flow.
如果这是你的答案我不会揍你的对吧
And if that's your answer,
I'm not gonna beat you up, right?
就像这样，这对很多球队来说都是有道理的。
Like that's okay, and
that makes sense for a lot of teams.
但我的确认为
But I do think that
there's a way to embrace
因为我觉得这也几乎是个回避问题
that because I really think that's almost
an avoidance of the issue as well.
这是一种不同的回避方式。
It's a different kind of avoidance.
你基本上是说 JavaScript 系统是无可救药的
You're basically saying
JavaScript system is hopeless,
所以我们要建立一个全新的系统
so let's build a whole new system.
那是另一种逃避，我不确定它是否健康。
That's a different kind of avoidance,
and I'm not sure that it's healthy.
所以， [COUGH]，我觉得 JavaScript 的类型不低，我觉得
So, [COUGH], I don't think JavaScript's
types are inferior, I think
他们可以被学习和利用我不认为这会更难
they can be learned and leveraged, and I
don't think it's that much more difficult.
其实我觉得学习这个系统是比较困难的
In fact, I think it's less difficult for
you to learn this system
学习的方式要比学习静态系统的所有复杂性都要正确。
taught properly than to go learn all
the complexities of a static type system.
我的意思是想都是老练的
I mean like thinking about
all the sophistication and
我认为这是一项非常艰巨的任务。
typescript, I would consider
that to be a very daunting task.
我想我想在这里讨论的是简单多的
And I think what I'm trying to
discuss here is a much simpler and
更小的东西要学
smaller thing to learn.
所以我的观点是，最好的方法就是拥抱 JavaScript 的类型
So my claim is that really the better
approach is to embrace JavaScript's types
并采用与该颗粒配合的编码方式，
and adopt the coding style
which goes with that grain,
让那些事情变得很明显
that makes those things obvious.
因此，您将获得更好的代码。
You are going to have
better code as a result.
通过思考这些事情
By thinking about those things,
你将会更好地构造你的代码，这几乎是不太理想的。
you are going to structure your code
better, that's almost undebatable.
但如果你仔细想想你的代码你会想到你的类型
But if you think about your code better
and you think about your types and
你把事情设计好让你明白他们在做什么
you design things so that you understand
what they're doing, you'll end up
设计更好的代码，并且代码更强大，它会减少错误。
designing better code, and that code will
be more robust, it'll have fewer bugs.
如果你不跟我的人平等
And that's if you do nothing
with the double equals,
想想你的类型吧
just think about your types, right?
你甚至不需要用双重平等的方式来获得这一利益。
You don't even have to use the double
equals to get that benefit.
所以如果你没有听到关于我的任何消息至少在这个单位
So if you hear nothing else about me,
at least from me on this unit,
至少听听这个
at least hear that.
你应该在你的代码里努力争取
You should be striving for
that in your code.
我认为您可以选择使用其他方法，并且
I think you can optionally choose
to use other approaches, and
也许我是其中之一
maybe Typl is one of several that could
开始存在于生态系统中除了这些极端之外还有其他选择
begin to exist in the ecosystem that give
other options besides these extremes.
所以希望能打开一些
So hopefully that is gonna open some
分析的不同途径其实我只要求你回去
different avenues of analysis, really
that's all I ask, is that you go back and
想想那些事情，测试我所做的断言，以及
think about those things, test out
the assertions that I'm making, and
看看他们是否对你和你的密码有意义
see if they make sense for
you and for your code.
但我很有信心你的代码质量会受到影响
But I'm quite confident that your
code quality will suffer if you
我不需要知道类型对吧
persist in the I don't need to know types,
right?
我最需要的是三重平等
Triple equals is all I ever need.
我觉得这不是更好的代码
I just don't think that's better code.
所以希望我给你点吃的
So, hopefully I've given you some food for
thought.
这就是我们课程的类型和胁迫的单位。
That is it for the types and
coercion unit of our course.